[{"question": "  oh, uh, hey rach. i uh, i was just coming over here to uh&#133; oh wait, i don&#146;t have to lie to you, you don&#146;t live here anymore. uh, i&#146;m eating their food. what are you doing?", "answer": " ross is on a date with my sister and they shut the drapes two and a-half-hours ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " i&#146;m good.", "answer": "  oh, are the drapes still closed hon?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " yeah. and y&#146;know who should&#146;ve shut their drapes? is that perverted old couple two doors over.", "answer": "  is that a swing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " oh don&#146;t even ask!", "answer": " yuck!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe ross went out with rachel&#146;s sister! when chandler made out with my sister i was mad at him for 10 years.", "answer": " that was like 5 years ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " yeah you got 5 years left!", "answer": " joey&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh ross, hi! hey, how are ya? there you are!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": "  i&#146;ll take a coffee.  so how was your big date last night?", "answer": " uhh, it was okay. yeah, it was fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah fun? great! so uh, so did you guys hit it off?", "answer": " i guess so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " so uh, so did anything happen? because rumor has it you guys shut the drapes!", "answer": " no. no. nothing happened. i shut the drapes to uh, show her slides of my favorite fossils.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh, slides.  so really nothing happened.", "answer": " something could&#146;ve happened. all right? she-she really dug my slides. and-and she was definitely giving me the vibe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " right. was it the, &quot;please don&#146;t show me another picture of a trilobite vibe?&quot;", "answer": " anyway, if she, if she wasn&#146;t in to me, why-why would she ask me out again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " she asked-asked you out again?", "answer": " yeah-uh-huh. tomorrow night, valentine&#146;s day, the most romantic day of the year. who knows what could happen? i might not be shutting my drapes to show her my slides, if you know what i mean.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " okay-okay-okay-okay-okay-okay-okay! i got it! i got it! i got it! i can&#146;t! i can&#146;t! i can&#146;t! i cannot go with you and my sister thing. okay? i just can&#146;t. it&#146;s just too weird, all right? i imagine the two of you together and i freak out. it freaks me out. i can&#146;t do it! i can&#146;t do it.", "answer": "  okay! okay! okay! it&#146;s okay.  it&#146;s okay. hey, it&#146;s too weird for you, i won&#146;t see her again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " thank you. i&#133;yeah.", "answer": " i mean after tomorrow night.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " no-no-no! no-no-no! please ross, i can&#146;t! i can&#146;t do it!  it&#146;s just gonna freak me out!!!", "answer": " okay! okay! ooh-hey-hey-hey! okay! okay! okay! i&#146;ll-i&#146;ll tell her tonight i can&#146;t see her anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " ross thanks.", "answer": " you want me to call her right now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh no! no! no-no-no-no! no, i mean come on that&#146;s-that&#146;s crazy&#151;i mean that&#146;s crazy. so what&#146;s-what&#146;s going on with you? what is going on with you?", "answer": " well umm, oh! i might be teaching another class this semester!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": "  this is my favorite part.", "answer": "  yeah me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " oh y&#146;know what&#146;s sadder than this? bambi. i cried for three days with that movie. no wait two! because on the third day my mother killed herself so i was partly crying for that.", "answer": "  well see now that i can see crying over, but bambi is a cartoon!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": "  you didn&#146;t cry when bambi&#146;s mother died?", "answer": " yes it was very sad when the guy stopped drawing the deer!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " chandler there&#146;s nothing wrong with crying! i mean you don&#146;t have to be so macho all the time.", "answer": " i&#146;m not macho.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " yeah you&#146;re right. i don&#146;t know what i was thinking.", "answer": " no, i guess i just never really cried. y&#146;know? i&#146;m not a crying kind of guy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " come on man there&#146;s gotta be something that gets you choked up! like uh, uh oh, what if you saw a three-legged puppy?", "answer": " i&#146;d be sad sure, but i wouldn&#146;t cry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " okay, what if the puppy said, &quot;help me chandler. all the other puppies pick on me.&quot;", "answer": " cry?! i just found a talking puppy, i&#146;m rich!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh, that&#146;s parent&#146;s day, first grade. that&#146;s me with the janitor martin.", "answer": " where were your parents?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " oh they didn&#146;t want to come!", "answer": " oh chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " poor thing!", "answer": " so that story doesn&#146;t make you cry?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " no! look, i don&#146;t cry! it&#146;s not a big deal! okay?!", "answer": " no! it&#146;s not okay! it&#146;s not okay at all!! you&#146;re dead inside!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " excuse me.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " are you phoebe buffay?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " wow! wow, thanks a lot! i just wanna say, i think you&#146;re really talented.", "answer": " you&#146;re just saying that because you&#146;re my biggest fan.   joey listen, take good care of that guy, okay?  he&#146;s a fan.  bye!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  so, you saw me on days of our lives huh? want me to, want me to do a little dr. drake remoray for ya?", "answer": " i have no idea what you&#146;re talking about. but i, but i just got phoebe buffay&#146;s autograph!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " oh, you&#146;re phoebe&#146;s fan!", "answer": " oh yeah! i&#146;ve seen all her movies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " movies?", "answer": " that was phoebe buffay, the porn star.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t think so.", "answer": " no-no, it was! she was in sex toy story 2, lawrence of alabia, and i got her autograph! the guys at the comic book store aren&#146;t gonna believe this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " hey gunther, don&#146;t let that guy in here anymore! he just said phoebe&#146;s a porn star!", "answer": " well, i wouldn&#146;t call her a star, but she&#146;s really good. you should check out inspecther gadget.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " you&#146;ll never believe what just happened, ross just totally blew me off and he didn&#146;t even tell me why!", "answer": " ohhh well. y&#146;know what honey? the best thing to do to get over a guy is to start dating someone else. oh! there is this great guy you will love at work named bob! he&#146;s a real up-and-comer in human resources.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " y&#146;know, thanks for trying to cheer me up, but i&#146;m not gonna date some random guy from your work.", "answer": " it&#146;s not random, it&#146;s bob.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " it&#146;s probably because not mature enough. or smart enough. maybe he doesn&#146;t like the way i dress&#151;no that can&#146;t be it. it&#146;s really gotta be the smart thing. oh i&#146;m so stupid! i&#146;m just like this incredibly pretty stupid girl!", "answer": " no honey, okay, okay, you wanna know why ross canceled the date? because i asked him to.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " you asked him too?!", "answer": " hm-mmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " why?!", "answer": " because you are my sister and ross and i have this huge history&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " i don&#146;t understand, do you want to go out with ross?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " you don&#146;t want him, but you don&#146;t want me to have him?", "answer": "  y&#146;know bob in human resources&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " ugh! i cannot believe you did this too me! you had me doubting how smart i was!  you had me doubting my fashion sense!", "answer": " look, this is not that big of a deal! you just don&#146;t date ross! there&#146;s a million other guys out there, you just&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hey! you have no right to tell me what to do.", "answer": " i&#146;m not telling you what to do! i am telling you what not to", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " why are you so jealous of me?", "answer": " jill this is not about me being jealous of you! this is about you being a brat! wanting what you can&#146;t have!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " all right, all right, well you just blew your chances at dating bob!", "answer": " who?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " &#133;i am jealous of her?! i mean who does she think she is?! princess caroline?!", "answer": " you&#146;re jealous of princess caroline?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " hey! uh, phoebe&#146;s not here is she?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  oh great! did you get a movie?", "answer": " uhhh, yeah. yeah. but uh, i don&#146;t think it&#146;s the kind you&#146;re gonna like.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " sort of&#133;", "answer": " guys, what&#146;s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  phoebe&#146;s a porn star!", "answer": " what?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " phoebe buffay in buffay: the vampire layer.", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " that&#146;s phoebe! where did you get that?", "answer": " well down at the adult video place down on bleaker.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " wow! i mean, i just&#151;i can&#146;t, i can&#146;t believe this. y&#146;know, i mean you think you know someone even, even phoebe who&#146;s always been somewhat of a question mark.", "answer": " this is so bizarre. i guess it kinda makes sense though, y&#146;know she had such a terrible childhood.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " hey, i had a terrible childhood and i don&#146;t do porn.", "answer": " yes, but you are dead inside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " all right well, i&#146;d better take that back.", "answer": " wh-what, why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " we can&#146;t watch that! i mean that&#146;s phoebe!", "answer": " yeah you&#146;re right, we can&#146;t&#151;we shouldn&#146;t watch this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " absolutely not.", "answer": "  y&#146;know maybe a little bit!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " probably just the first half.", "answer": " no! hey no! this is wrong you guys! phoebe&#146;s our friend! well, i&#146;m not gonna watch it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah! good for you joe!", "answer": " yeah.  (the movie starts, it&#146;s a vampire&#146;s lair and buffay, the vampire layer enters dressed in leather and carrying a wooden stake. suddenly, the vampire opens his coffin and sits up. buffay, the vampire layer: ah, i thought i&#146;d find you here, nasforatool.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " hold on a second! what is that on her ankle?", "answer": " her ankle is what you&#146;re watching?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " well it&#146;s hard to tell&#133;  oh god, if she would just stop moving.", "answer": " she&#146;s just doing her job!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": "  you sick bastards!", "answer": " oh, it&#146;s a tattoo! that&#146;s weird, phoebe doesn&#146;t&#133; wait that&#146;s ursula! that&#146;s not phoebe that is ursula!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " re! re! then i can watch that! rewind it! rewind it!", "answer": "  hey! what&#146;s up?  oh my god! what am i doing?!! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey sweetie!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": "  chicken soup for the soul?", "answer": " there&#146;s no back to this couch!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " why are you reading this? you hate this kind of stuff.", "answer": " yeah i know, but i figured a shot y&#146;know? maybe one of those stories would make me cry and then you wouldn&#146;t think i was y&#146;know, all dead inside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " oh that&#146;s so sweet! look chandler i don&#146;t care if you can&#146;t cry, i love you.", "answer": " oh that makes me feel so warm in my hollow tin chest.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " stop it!", "answer": " no, i mean, come on, seriously think about it, we get married, we&#146;re up at the altar and i&#146;m like this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah! and if, and if we have a baby one-day, and the doctor hands it to you in the delivery room and you don&#146;t cry, so what! and-and-and, and if we take him to college and come home and see his empty room for the first time, and you got nothing, it won&#146;t matter to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " okay, well i won&#146;t uh, worry about this anymore then.", "answer": " and-and-and if i die, from a long illness. and you&#146;re writing out my eulogy and you open a desk drawer and you find a note from me that says, &quot;i will always be with you,&quot; and you still can&#146;t shed one tiny tear, i know you&#146;ll be crying a river inside.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " aww, i love you so&#133;", "answer": " what is wrong with you?!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " what?! you can&#146;t shed a tear for your dead wife!! now, i left you a note from the beyond!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " so you didn&#146;t mean any of that?!", "answer": " no you robot!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " you damn kids! you ring my bell one more time, i swear to&#133;  ohh, uh jill. umm, that-that&#146;s just a little game i play with the kids down the hall. umm, they&#146;ve really taken a liking to me.  uhh what&#146;s-what&#146;s-what&#146;s the matter?", "answer": " rachel and i had a really big fight, can i come in? i-i mean i know we&#146;re not supposed to see each other anymore and i&#146;m okay with that, it&#146;s just that i don&#146;t know anybody in the city and i really need somebody to talk to about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": "  i don&#146;t want to talk about it.", "answer": " okay, umm&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " but you know what might really cheer me up?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " seeing some more of your super-cool slides.", "answer": " wow! really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " totally, i love them! and, maybe you could finish telling me about all the different kinds of sand.", "answer": " well, i&#146;d love to! here, you wait right here and i&#146;ll go get the projector and my notes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh great! thanks ross, you&#146;re such a good friend!", "answer": " ohh! (he goes into another room to get his projector and notes. while he&#146;s gone, jill quickly checks her makeup.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " hey! have you guys seen jill? i can&#146;t find her anywhere.", "answer": " no, i haven&#146;t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " who is it?", "answer": " it&#146;s phoebe! phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  oh god. so-so you&#146;re making porn movies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " we&#146;re still rolling!", "answer": " you&#146;re making one right now! another man&#146;s voice: let&#146;s go phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " and-and you&#146;re using my name!", "answer": " yeah, can i help you with something? same man&#146;s voice: phoebe, come on!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " look, i&#146;m talking right now! you&#146;re&#151;you mean her.", "answer": " y&#146;know, twin stuff is always a real big seller.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " yeah, i can talk them into giving you like, 30 dollars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " slides are almost ready.", "answer": " yeah. ooh, i know what this is missing! alcohol!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " uh okay, well there&#146;s-there&#146;s wine in the kitchen.", "answer": " oh great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": "  hello?", "answer": "  what is my sister doing there?! and why are the drapes shut?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " o-okay, rach calm-calm down, okay? she-she&#146;s really upset we&#146;re just talking.", "answer": " ross! i think she is trying to make something happen with you to get back at me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " so that&#146;s the only reason she could be here huh? it couldn&#146;t have anything to do with the fact that-that maybe i&#146;m a good listener and i uh i put on a great slide show!", "answer": " ross, i am telling you that she is using you to get back at me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " y&#146;know what? i think i can take care of myself, i&#146;ll talk to you later. good-bye.  whoa! uh, that was your sister actually. she-she thinks that you&#146;re just using me.", "answer": " so?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " so, i just came from the company ursula works for.", "answer": " oh no, not you too!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " no! no! i just went to pick up phoebe buffay&#146;s checks; there were a lot of them.", "answer": " nice!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " um-mmm, and i won&#146;t have to go there anymore because i gave them my correct address.", "answer": " that&#146;s great, but isn&#146;t it gonna bother that people still think you&#146;re a porn star?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " oh no! no! i know how to handle it.", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " yeah.   you&#146;re trying to figure out where you know me from? all right, i&#146;ll give you a hint. from porn! okay?  yeah your pervert boyfriend watched me in a porno movie!  see?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": "  you uh, you may have been right about jill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " oh! i knew it! what happened?", "answer": " umm, she kissed me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " what?! you kissed!", "answer": "  maybe we should give them some privacy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": "  shhhh!!!", "answer": " look, i uh, i tried not to kiss her, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " well, it doesn&#146;t sound like it! i mean, it&#146;s pretty easy not to kiss someone, you just don&#146;t kiss them! see look at us, right now, not kissing!", "answer": " let me finish, okay? she started kissing me and-and i didn&#146;t stop it. i guess i-i just wasn&#146;t thinking&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " oh wait&#151;hold it! but then i started thinking and i stopped the kissing.", "answer": " oh, well thank you for taking your tongue out of my sister&#146;s mouth long enough to tell me that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " look i-i realize if anything were to happen with me and jill then nothing could ever happen with us!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " no, i mean, look i don&#146;t know if anything is going to happen with us, again. ever. but i don&#146;t want to know that it-it never could. so i stopped it and she got mad and broke my projector.", "answer": " wow. i, i don&#146;t even know what to say. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " oh my god! are-are you crying?", "answer": "  i just don&#146;t see why those two can&#146;t work things out! ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " all right, i&#146;m leaving! because i&#146;m not going to spend one more day with someone whose out to sabotage my every move. that&#146;s you rachel!", "answer": " yeah, i got that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": "  and you! i throw myself at you and you say no, how gay are you?", "answer": " you take care jill.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " bye-bye-e!", "answer": " bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}]